I just have a couple more questions for you.
- Hey. Where's Lisbon?
- She's in court.
You know you're late.
Yeah, I must have turned
my alarm clock off. Overslept.
Hot date?
What are you talking about?
Well, you know.
Duncan. From L.A.
- Wayne, it's not like that.
- Oh, right. Sure.
You mind finishing up
these interviews?
Hi.
- That's it, sir.
- Thanks.
Van Pelt's here now.
Is Jane coming?
I don't know. Call him.
Hey, Rigsby.
What's going on?
Uh, you know we have
a case, right?
Yeah. I heard.
I'm, uh, kind of busy here,
so I'm not gonna make it.
He's not gonna make it.
- Yeah, but I'm happy to help.
- Help how?
Well, you two talk to me, and I'll listen.
You'll be my eyes and my ears.
Okay, I'll put you on speaker.
Cho. Tell Jane what we got.
Housewife. Missy Roberts. 32.
Maid found her
shot in the bathroom.
Now, there's bullet holes in the hallway
and one in the closet door here.
"So it looks like a fight started elsewhere
then she ran to the bathroom."
"Forensics recovered
9-millimeter casings."
Eh, forensics.
Tell me about the body.
Well, she's lying here
on the floor in gym clothes.
She's been shot in the chest,
uh, once in the foot
and there's two bullet holes
lodged in the ground
so we're not dealing
with an expert marksman.
Well, maybe, maybe not.
Uh, what about the husband?
"Yeah. Husband."
Name's Kip. He runs a high-end
home electronics company.
"He left town 2 days ago on some boondoggle
white-water rafting trip to Tahoe."
- Interesting. How did he take the news?
- "Well, he hasn't gotten it yet."
His office says the rafting group will be
out of cell range for another day or so.
- Describe to me the bedroom.
- Why?
Well, I want to understand their
relationship. A bedroom says a lot.
Okay.
All right, it's, uh...
Cold, impersonal.
Tightly made bed.
- "No pictures."
- Let's try the kitchen.
Okay.
- Okay. What am I looking for?
- Tell me what's in the fridge.
Butter, milk, eggs...
Baking stuff.
Which makes sense,
because there are these
awesome looking cupcakes
on the counter.
They're, uh, red velvet, I think.
Yeah. What else is in the fridge?
A bunch of diet shakes and soda.
- Is the victim heavy?
- Oh, no, she's very thin.
- What about Kip?
- I guess he's kind of chubby.
But it looks like he sees
a personal trainer, though.
Oh, this is not
a happy marriage.
Kip's portly but fights it.
Missy is naturally thin
and a gourmet baker.
He views her hobby
as a sabotage and resents it.
"She views his dieting as a lack
of interest in her personal outlet."
You need to talk to Kip.
He wants us to talk to Kip.
We can't
not until tomorrow.
"Oh, please, this is the last guy
who'd go on a white-water rafting trip."
You don't hire a personal trainer
'cause you like strenuous activity.
You hire a personal trainer
because it's the only possible
way to get yourself to do it.
So you think he lied
about the trip?
Well, I'm almost certain.
So if he's not white-water
rafting, where is he?
Well, I don't know, but I'm sure
you two will figure it out.
And, Rigsby...
Put the cupcake back.
"Lisbon, I can hear you skulking
around out there. What is it?"
We've got a case.
You can deal with Red John later.
Yeah, Missy Roberts.
I already broke that wide open.
Yeah, I heard.
The old rafting trip gambit?
Yep, exactly.
Except for Kip Roberts
texted a picture of himself
to Missy right before she died.
He's holding a paddle next
to a river with a raft full of bozos.
Trick photography.
The Tahoe cops are gonna
go pick him up
but in the meantime, let's go
talk to the victim's sister.
Jane, I need you.
It's nice to be needed.
Anything for you, Lisbon.
We're very sorry for your loss, Emma.
Were you and your sister close?
Missy was like
a second mother to me but...
you know, now we're just...
in different places in our lives
so I just hadn't seen her
in a while.
Did she say if she was having
any problems recently?
I knew that she was tired
of... staying at home
you know, and...and, like,
not feeling useful
and I think that that was why
she started volunteering... at the bakery.
- Where?
- The O.G. Bakery.
It's this nonprofit
where they...
They teach ex-cons new skills,
you know like baking and...
She started there
a few months ago.
Was anybody giving her
trouble there?
- Not that I know of.
- Were Missy and Kip, uh...
Trying anything
to save their marriage?
About a month ago, they...
went on this radio show
with this Love Doctor guy and...
I think they were seeing him
privately also.
A love doctor, huh?
Some... Buddy... something,
I don't know.
- Henner or...
- Buddy Hennings?
He has a talk radio show... "Prescription
For Love with Buddy Hennings".
What? I've listened to it
in my car a few times.
All right. I'll go talk
to Buddy Hennings
the Love Doctor, and you
check out the shady bakery.
Van Pelt and Rigsby can handle that.
I'll go to the radio station with you.
- Ahh... that's 'cause you're a fan.
- I am not!
Look, I just think
he's a viable lead.
It's all right, Lisbon.
We all have our guilty pleasures.
- Oh, this must be very exciting for you.
- That's enough.
Hey, Van Pelt.
What'd you find out?
Turns out one of the ex-cons
at the bakery was still selling drugs...
a girl named Monica Suarez, 20.
Missy found out and reported her
to the bakery supervisor.
Well, what's Monica's deal?
"She's been in the system
since she was 14."
Vandalism, assault, dealing.
She just got out of Chowchilla
six months ago.
Ah. Real sweetheart.
"Yeah, that's what the bakery
supervisor said."
After Missy reported Monica,
Missy's tires were slashed.
She said she saw Monica
following her around a few times.
All right, you and Riggs
go and pick her up.
All right.
"They're celebrating the opening..."
Hi. We need to speak
with Buddy Hennings.
If you want to be on the show
you have to fill out this form
and take it to couples-intake.
Oh, we're not a couple.
Please.
What she means is ours is
more of a platonic love.
Buddy Hennings, please.
He's on the air.
Talk to his producer.
She's a huge fan.
She's a little... very excited. Yeah.
Sean, what I'm hearing from you
is that Lisa has become sexually cold
ever since the baby was born.
Oh, excuse me. This...this isn't
a good time. Can I help you?
I'm Agent Lisbon
with the CBI.
- This is Patrick Jane.
- Hi.
We're investigating the murder
of Missy Roberts.
I'm... I'm sorry to hear about
that, but we're live here.
Come here, please.
You have to excuse
our producer Gary.
He's a bit of a control freak.
Thinks everyone's out to ruin his show.
Well, just 'cause he's paranoid
doesn't mean they're not out to get him.
- Who are you?
- I'm Elizabeth Hennings.
- Hi.
- I'm Buddy's wife and manager.
Uh, we heard about Missy.
It's just awful.
We need to talk to Buddy.
Okay, well, it's gonna be
a little while, all right?
'Cause we're in the middle
of a segment
then we have to shoot
a promo for a Webcast, so...
That's all right. We like to watch.
Don't we?
look at each other in the eye.
- Look at this. Look at this.
- Please don't touch anything.
No, I won't.
Thank you, Mr. Lewis.
Monica's parole officer said
it's the right address.
- So we keep waiting.
- Yup.
Stakeouts are the worst.
Wayne, is something wrong?
No. There's nothing wrong. I...
I've been feeling kinda weird
since you've been back.
Yeah, you've been acting
kind of weird.
- What's up with that?
- It's just...
When you were in L.A.,
I had time to think...
- About you. About us.
- Okay. And?
Well, I mean,
did you think about me at all?
Of course I did.
Yeah...
Wait...
is that her on the left?
Uh, yeah. Come on.
Monica Suarez?
Hey!
CBI!
Get out of the way!
Police!
Come here.
Get your hands off me!
I got nothing on me!
Yeah, 'cause you threw
your stash in the dumpster.
- You good?
- Yeah, you?
Yeah.
Talk to me
about Missy Roberts.
- Who?
- She was murdered last night.
First I heard of it.
But you messed with her
when she got you fired, right?
I was still on parole.
I... I needed that job.
So you slashed her tires,
stalked her?
I... I just followed her around,
you know, to freak her out.
Oh, yeah?
You see anything interesting?
Not really. I mean, you know,
she went shoe shopping
and got mani-pedis a lot...
you know, rich lady stuff.
- Where were you last night?
- I was at my cousin's quinceañera.
- All night.
- All right. Come on.
Let's go!
"This is Buddy Hennings with
Prescription For Love."
"We'll be back in ten minutes,
right after the news."
Buddy, these people are from CBI.
They're, uh, here about Missy.
Buddy Hennings.
Glad to help any way I can.
Buddy, we have a phone call
with the publisher in about a half hour.
- So, if you all don't need me...
- Oh, by all means.
I know you're a busy man.
We just have a few questions.
Missy and Kip... they were
on your show a while back?
Yes. Good people, both of them.
Some of the couples we get in here
they're really just here for their 15 minutes
but I had a feeling that Missy
really wanted to work on her marriage.
That's why I offered
to see them privately.
And when was the last time
you saw them?
Last week. Thursday.
Supposed to come in this week,
but she called to cancel.
She didn't give a reason.
You know what? I have to take this.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Well, listen, Buddy,
while we're just chatting
just you and I here,
hanging out, a couple of guys
- do you think Kip could have done it?
- No. Absolutely not.
But you said it was Missy that wanted
help with their marriage, not Kip.
Well, I think in the beginning
he was going along to get along
- but he turned a corner.
- How so?
Well, in the first few sessions
he was very distant
very uncooperative,
both with me and with Missy.
But then, after
a couple of sessions
he developed an attentiveness and a warmth
that I hadn't seen in him before.
- He really changed.
- Maybe.
- You don't agree?
- Well...
You know, maybe he was just covering.
He felt guilty for something,
like having an affair.
- I saw no signs of an affair.
- Oh, come on.
The recent drive
to get in shape
suddenly doting on his wife
that he'd been neglecting for years.
Well, I would like to think that
he was responding to the treatment.
- Ah. Good point.
- Hi. Um...
Would you mind giving us
a minute alone?
- I'm sorry.
- Sure thing.
The cops finally tracked down
the rafting group.
It turns out Kip skipped out
after the first night.
Hmm. I hate to say
I told you so.
And we still don't know
where he is.
His last credit card charge was yesterday
at a gas station outside of Tahoe.
The attendant remembers him
being with a blonde woman.
Plot thickens.
Or should I say thins?
Let's go back to the CBI.
I'm gonna put out a BOLO.
BOLO shmolo. We need
to reach a wider audience.
And how do you propose
we do that?
Welcome back to KZHC
where we play the smooth sounds
of the '80s and the '90s.
I'm Patrick Jane from the California
Bureau of Investigation.
Yes, that is something
that does exist.
And we're throwing a contest today
because we need your help
to find a car,
a very important car
that will help us break
a very important case.
We're looking for a silver
Mercedes S-class
license plate "KIPMAN7"...
The first person to call in
the location of this car
will receive $10,000 cash money.
Yes, folks, we're talking ca...
whoop. Wait.
I just got word
from my producer
that that is not the amount
of the prize. It is actually...
$20...
And the chance to guest deejay
here at the radio station...
Day and date of your choosing.
That's right, folks.
Guest deejay spot
during drive time
and in case you missed it, I'll put
all the details up on the CBI web site.
Do we have a CBI web site?
Yes, that nice... CBI web site.
Excellent. Now let's see
those phone lines light up.
Talk to me, please.
Talk to me, people.
Come on, Sacramento.
- "Uh, when did they check in?"
- Yesterday. Room 311
under her name... Rosie Dunlop.
Was she fit? Muscular?
- Yeah.
- Personal trainer.
Okay.
Gonna be like that.
Mr. Roberts, this is CBI!
Open the door!
Mr. Roberts, we're coming in!
Jane?
Please. Don't shoot. Please.
- Please...
- Kip Roberts?
I'm Agent Lisbon with the CBI.
Jungle theme.
It's classy.
Who are you?
What's going on?
Mr. Roberts, are you being
held against your will?
No, not at all.
No, we're consenting adults.
You gotta believe me.
Oh, I believe you.
Missy was... kind.
Selfless.
But she wanted kids.
And after a bunch of miscarriages,
we... drifted apart.
- It's my fault. I know.
- Probably. You cheated on her.
I never meant to hurt Missy.
And... and Rosie's
the only one, I swear.
I'm not... I'm not one
of those guys, you know?
- How long was the affair going on?
- A few months.
I mean, I tried to stop, but...
I struggle with willpower.
And...
There were certain... Things
about Rosie that I liked
things that were
maybe missing from my marriage.
You mean Rosie gets rough
with you. You like that.
Yeah.
You think Missy knew
about the affair?
I don't know. Maybe.
It was weird.
She called me
while I was driving up to Tahoe.
Said she wanted to make it work
that she never gave up on us...
- That she would always love me.
- And that's weird?
It was the most intimate conversation
we'd had in years.
And I vowed to myself
that I would break things off
with Rosie as soon as I got
to the hotel.
- Did you?
- Yes.
But...
Rosie is a very passionate woman.
And when I try to break
things off, she hits me.
And when she hits me
- I get turned on.
- The heart wants what it wants.
Do we have any closer photos
of Missy's closet?
I don't know.
There's a whole other
stack of pictures.
I just finished with Kip.
He seemed genuinely upset
about his wife.
- Then again, he was cheating on her.
- I talked to Rosie, the mistress.
She said her and Kip were drinking at the
hotel bar at the time of Missy's death.
She has every reason to lie.
Hold on to Kip and her
until their alibis check out.
Was Missy's home
very neat?
You know, an "everything
in its place" type of house?
Yeah. Why?
I'm going back
to the radio station.
I need to take a look at that,
Webcast thingy of Missy and Kip.
Why?
I need to see Missy's feet.
Hello? KZHC.
Let me check.
- Hey there.
- Hey!
Oh, God.
You gave me a start.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, you know. Investigating.
Well, I'm... sorry I was late.
I had an appointment.
You found Kip Roberts,
I presume.
Oh, yes, yes.
It worked like a charm.
In fact, it worked so well
I'm gonna ask you for another favor.
Shoot.
I need to see Missy and Kip's
episode of your show.
Do you have a copy
around here anywhere?
Well, I sure don't.
- But I'll bet Gary could help you.
- Great.
I mean, Michael and I have been
together six months but...
sometimes I feel like we're missing
a deeper connection, you know?
Buddy will definitely get into that
with you on the show tomorrow.
- You agree with Shayna?
- 100%.
Really? 100%? Not 98% or 99%?
The full, even 100%?
Wow, Buddy's not gonna have
much to work with here.
- Mr. Jane.
- Hi.
- What a pleasure.
- Yeah, always.
I need to see, uh, the Webcast
of Missy and Kip's episode.
Could you get that
for me, please?
- Sure. But it'll take a minute.
- Good. Time to make a cup of tea.
"So, Missy and Kip."
"Why don't you begin by telling us
a little bit about your marriage?"
- Is this the only angle you've got?
- "We've been married 12 years."
It's a Webcast...
Not Steven Spielberg.
"We're here because
we're just not as close..."
- Of course. Thank you.
- "Well, I appreciate your honesty."
"And I know it's scary but it's like
I always say, if nothing changes..."
"Nothing changes."
Rigsby, it's Jane.
I need you to go back
to Missy Roberts' house.
- Okay, for what?
- "A pair of sexy gold sandals."
I didn't them in her shoe rack
but I need you to look everywhere.
Copy that.
Just so that we're clear
how would you define sexy?
You'll know it when you see it.
Hey, these are gold.
I'm not sure how sexy
they are.
They're not sexy.
And they're beige.
Hey, you know that
Van Pelt's dating someone?
- Yeah.
- We sort of talked about us today.
Not really, but... kind of.
It was weird.
What do you think?
I think we need to call Jane.
They're not here.
- Hey, Cho. Any luck?
- They're not here.
Well, as expected.
Oh, there is one more thing.
Ask Rigsby what size shoe
Van Pelt is.
"What size shoe
does Van Pelt wear?"
Uh, I wanna say an 8,
a 7 and a half if they run big.
- 8.
- Excellent.
The hotel bar has video surveillance.
Kip and Rosie's alibi check out.
- So we're back to square one.
- Don't be so sure.
I have a very exciting
assignment for you, Grace.
- You do? Cool. What is it?
- These are for you. Try 'em on.
- Nothing for me?
- Trust me. You won't like 'em.
- They're really high.
- Try 'em on.
Go on.
Take 'em for a little spin.
That is what I'm talking about.
Right there.
- How do they look?
- Perfect.
Jane, you want to tell me
what's going on?
Well, let's just say
the game is afoot.
Two feet.
- So what's your play here?
- Oh, no play.
- I'm gonna help 'em.
- Right.
Michael. Shayna.
- Hi.
- Hold on a sec.
Patrick Jane.
I met you yesterday in the studio.
Are you guys excited
about being on the show?
- Yes, I can't wait.
- Totally, yeah.
Yeah. Sure.
Shayna, why don't you
go ahead?
There's just one thing I want
to go over with Michael.
- Okay. I'll wait over there.
- All right.
Hey, are you still there?
Look at that, huh?
- Yeah...
- All right, listen, Michael
you don't have to do this
if you don't want to.
You don't have to go
on the radio.
Yeah. Of course I know that.
I wanna go.
Well, you can lie to me. I don't care.
But don't lie to yourself.
I know you think Shayna's
out of your league
and you don't wanna
rock the boat.
That's why you agree
with everything she says.
Okay, that's just...
that's just not true.
Okay? I just think
that she's right... a lot.
When was the last time you were
completely honest with her?
Last time you disagreed with her
on something important?
Okay.
All right, all right, fine.
Maybe... maybe you're right.
I don't want to lose her.
- I get it. I get that.
- You know?
But you're gonna go in there.
And you're gonna tell her, "Hey, babe"
"I don't want to go
on this show."
I mean, who in their
right mind
wants to air their dirty
laundry on the radio
for other people's
entertainment?
It is a terrible idea.
And she will respect you
for making a stand.
- You really think so?
- Oh, yes.
Women love a strong man.
Besides, have you
listened to the show?
- It's crap.
- Yeah, yeah, it is.
- You're right.
- That's right.
- I'm not gonna do it.
- You're not.
- I'm not.
- No.
- That's it.
- That's it, man.
- Pound it.
- Thank you very much.
All right.
Oh, thank God. There you are.
What's the matter?
Tonight's couple...
Shayna and Michael... just canceled.
15 minutes out.
Well, there's a young couple
there in intake.
They're nice-looking kids.
Can you prep them
in time for the show?
I'm gonna have to.
Excuse me.
Just move!
Okay. Change of plans, guys.
You're going on in five.
Oh, that's great news,
isn't it, babe?
Sure, sweetie.
Okay. Stay there.
All right?
- "Thanks for listening I'll be back..."
- 4:00. We're up.
"Howdy, everybody. This is Buddy
Hennings on Prescription For Love"
coming to you live
from KZHC here in Sacramento
and right here
in the studio with us today
we have Dwayne and Stace.
Welcome to you both.
- Hi.
We're happy to be here.
Long-time listeners, first-time... guests.
Well, why don't you begin by telling us
a little bit about why you're here?
We're having some
communication issues.
What does that mean, exactly?
Oh, you know, we're having trouble
like, uh, talking to each other.
Dwayne, how about you not pee
on my head and call it rain?
Excuse me?
If you want to get better,
you're gonna have to get real for me
so why don't you begin by telling me
something I don't know?
We have kind of a...
rocky history.
"We've been on and off for
about five years... mostly off."
"Yeah, we met on the job."
There was a "no fraternization"
policy, but we, um...
- Fraternized.
- A lot.
Well, now we're getting
somewhere.
- How's the sex?
- Well...
It's been a while, but when we have it
it's... it's good.
- Yes?
- Yes.
We should not be
listening to this, really.
Oh, come on, Lisbon.
Don't be such a prude.
"You're young and vibrant."
A little too soon in the game
to be calling a time-out.
There's just a lot of, uh... baggage
left over from all the off periods.
Why did you break up?
Well, I th... I think
we broke up the first time
because you decided that
the job was more important.
Right? Wasn't that it?
Yeah, well, then you got
Sarah pregnant.
Yeah, after you got
engaged to a maniac.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
We don't use exaggeration here.
It's no help to us at all.
"Maniac," no.
Maybe you didn't approve.
That's fair game.
Let's get back to the baby.
Is that true, Dwayne?
No.
Uh, yes. I had a baby
with someone else
but we were off.
Totally off.
What about the engagement?
It didn't work out.
- Yeah, because he's a homicidal maniac.
- Fine.
"Relationships can be brutal."
"And for the record,
I'm not angry about the baby."
"Oh, really? 'Cause I never thought you were
angry, but you sound kinda angry now."
"No, I just
thought it was weird"
that you would have a baby
with someone you barely knew.
Well, why don't you tell me
what you really think?
- But...
- But what? What else is there?
But I love that you're a dad.
You do?
When we got together,
we were kids.
I was a young, naive girl.
I wasn't ready to commit to you.
It wasn't about the job.
At least that wasn't all of it.
But things have changed since then.
We're not the same.
And that's okay.
I like who I am now.
I like who you are.
You're a man.
You guys are fantastic.
So real.
Before we go, is there anything you two
would like to say to each other?
No. Yes.
Just...
I'm sorry.
For a lot of things.
I care about you
and I never meant to hurt you.
All right, your turn.
Anything?
You know how I feel about you.
It's the same way I've always felt.
It's never changed.
Since the first day I met you.
Well, then my work
is done here.
Thank you for listening
to Prescription For Love
This is Buddy Hennings
on KZHC talk radio.
Bravo.
- That was a fantastic show.
- Thanks. That was really helpful.
Yeah. Yeah, it was.
Thanks, doc.
Excuse me.
- Hello?
- Great job, Rigsby.
Oh, hi, boss.
Wow. Tonight? Really?
Yeah. I'll be right there.
Okay. Bye.
I'm so sorry, babe.
It's the Carson job.
I have to go into work.
Uh, you okay to take a cab home?
Oh. Sure. Go.
- Um... see you later.
- Yeah.
- Thanks again, Doc.
- My pleasure.
And don't you worry about her.
We'll take good care of her.
Thanks.
Stace, you know, you have
a natural presence on radio.
I mean it.
You are a natural.
Are you saying I have
a face for radio?
Oh, no, no, not at all.
You are definitely drop-dead gorgeous.
You know, I think maybe
you two could benefit
from some private sessions.
Would you be up for that?
Oh. Thank you.
That's so nice of you.
Oh, my pleasure.
Just make sure you call my office.
Can I call you a cab?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you for everything.
I'm... I'll see you soon.
Um, do you mind if I...
Okay. See you later.
What happened?
Oh, my heel broke.
I think I twisted my ankle.
That does look bad.
All right, we'll get you
to my office, and we'll...
"we'll get some ice on it.
Come on."
"Come on."
- Hey. How's it going?
- Perfect.
The heel thing worked a treat.
Van Pelt is now alone
with the killer.
There we go.
That should help
with the swelling.
- It's cold.
- Yeah.
- May I?
- Sure.
How does that feel?
"It feels pretty good, actually."
He's really into feet.
How did you know that?
Eh, it was kind of obvious,
don't you think?
I wouldn't be asking if it was.
Well, she was shot in the foot
and her shoes were missing.
The shoes that she wore
the first time she met Buddy.
That's it?
Well, no. He also has a large
picture of a woman's foot
in a ballet shoe
en pointe in his office.
He gets manicures at the salon.
He likes to watch women
get pedicures.
Gross.
Yeah. Are we listening here, folks?
"My ankle's actually feeling better
but don't stop."
You have amazing feet.
- I do?
- Yes.
Thanks.
There's nothing sexier
than an amazing foot in an amazing shoe.
Yeah, those were my favorite pair.
What am I gonna wear home?
Well, I think I may be able
to help you with that.
- Yeah?
- Hold on.
- Don't go anywhere.
- Okay.
You're about a 7 and a half,
8, right?
Yeah.
Well, I think these
should work out.
Yes, I think that will work
just perfectly.
Those gold sandals are gorgeous.
I love them.
That's our cue.
Let's go!
Whoa! Put the gun down!
Don't shoot.
Uh, wasn't expecting that.
You talk to people for a living.
But you couldn't talk to me
tell me what you needed.
I wanted to be enough for you
but I could not compete with...
That.
Elizabeth, please, sweetheart.
Please, please put the gun down!
Just relax, take it easy,
and nobody will get hurt.
Really, sweetie?
Because you should see
what I did with the last one.
Elizabeth, no.
No, please tell me you didn't.
What choice did I have?
You weren't gonna stop.
You're not gonna stop.
CBI! Don't move!
Put the gun on the table!
Do it!
Hands behind your back.
You're under arrest.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Thank you.
"I had some trysts
a few years back."
When the show hit big,
I knew I'd have to control myself.
- I love Elizabeth.
- Why Missy?
I don't expect you to understand this.
She had the highest arches
I've ever seen.
Exquisite.
The ballistics report proves
the bullets came from your gun.
He was sleeping with her,
and you couldn't stand that.
Grace, is it?
You're a pretty young thing.
But it won't last forever.
You think he's still gonna want you
when you're my age?
Of course I couldn't stand it.
He was lying.
And sneaking around
like a horny teenager.
With her.
She called me to her house
to end it.
She said she felt guilty,
taken advantage of.
They wanted to make
their marriage work.
- You try to change her mind?
- Oh, yeah, but it didn't work.
She wouldn't take me back.
That's when I asked her
for something to...
remember her by.
"That's when she gave me
the shoes."
"Just to get rid of me, I guess."
I just wanted to scare her a little.
Tell her to leave him alone.
"But then she had the nerve
to call him a creep"
"like she was too good
for him."
"I lost it."
"And then I still had
all this rage."
And I have to admit...
It felt good.
Your brow is furrowed.
You have that squinty look in your eye.
You wanna talk to me
about the whole foot fetish thing...
But the catholic schoolgirl in you tells you
that it's not necessarily appropriate.
You're right. Look, I don't get it.
I can't wrap my head around it.
Well, I mean, "fetish" is a strong word
but everyone has that thing.
- It's just... It's human nature.
- I don't.
Oh, come on, Lisbon.
Don't deny yourself that freedom.
There's definitely something
out there that works for you
that flips your switch.
- Like turtlenecks.
- You're right. It's inappropriate.
- Good night.
- Turtlenecks it is.
- Hey.
- Hey. What's up?
Yeah?